{
    "Questions":
    [
        {
        "Question":"Who wants to take Charlize Theron to a dinner date?",
        "Option1":"Kiran",
        "Option2":"Sucheta",
        "Option3":"Harshad",
        "Option4":"Pushkar",
        "Correct":"Kiran"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Who idolize Gautam Buddha?",
        "Option1":"Rahul ",
        "Option2":"Pushkar",
        "Option3":"Kiran",
        "Option4":"Harshad",
        "Correct":"Harshad"
        },
        {
        "Question":"What was the purpose of initials - rd and jd?",
        "Option1":"File Extensions",
        "Option2":"Cool Dudes",
        "Option3":"Founders",
        "Option4":"Famous Musicians",
        "Correct":"File Extensions"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Who is Non-engineer among our team?",
        "Option1":"Rahul",
        "Option2":"Kiran",
        "Option3":"Harshad",
        "Option4":"Pushkar",
        "Correct":"Pushkar"
        },
        {
        "Question":"How many years did Rahul live in the USA?",
        "Option1":"13",
        "Option2":"11",
        "Option3":"14",
        "Option4":"10",
        "Correct":"14"
        },
        {
        "Question":"What is Pushkars additional skills that lets him judge people?",
        "Option1":"Acting",
        "Option2":"Directing",
        "Option3":"NLP",
        "Option4":"Dieting",
        "Correct":"NLP"
        },
        {
        "Question":"What does Kiran say more than any other word?",
        "Option1":"You know",
        "Option2":"Essentially",
        "Option3":"Really",
        "Option4":"Hmmm",
        "Correct":"Essentially"
        },
        {
        "Question":"What business unit does Kiran lead?",
        "Option1":"Manufacturing",
        "Option2":"Partnerships",
        "Option3":"Healthcare",
        "Option4":"LabTech",
        "Correct":"Partnerships"
        },
        {
        "Question":"What skill Harshad is not good at?",
        "Option1":"Quality",
        "Option2":"Creativity",
        "Option3":"Communication",
        "Option4":"Dancing",
        "Correct":"Dancing"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Who wants to roam age of dinosaurs?",
        "Option1":"Rahul",
        "Option2":"Sucheta",
        "Option3":"Pushkar",
        "Option4":"Kiran",
        "Correct":"Sucheta"
        },
        {
        "Question":"What is Suchetas new role?",
        "Option1":"HR",
        "Option2":"Finance",
        "Option3":"Operations",
        "Option4":"Marketing Communication",
        "Correct":"Marketing Communication"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Who joined Ethosh between 2015 June to 2017 June?",
        "Option1":"Pushkar",
        "Option2":"Sucheta",
        "Option3":"Harshad",
        "Option4":"Kiran",
        "Correct":"Kiran"
        }
    ]
}
